Is this just all part of a deal that's been done with Hamas?
They released Thai citizens and the hostages have to all say they were treated well.
When we negotiated with Hamas, they didn't give any requests or conditions for release.
They just said that the Thai hostages would be freed when there's a ceasefire.
But Hamas did kill at least 39 Thai citizens.
39 Thais were killed, that's for sure.
But we don't know where or how.
It's a war.
It is indisputable that families were murdered by Hamas on October 7th.
Why did you feel so sure that they would protect hostages?
Definitely, it is a war.
There was killing on both sides.
But the main point of Hamas going there was to capture hostages
and to use them for deals to help the Palestinians.
Just to be clear, you're not denying that Hamas killed Israeli civilians, are you?
According to Hamas, they only wanted to kill Israeli soldiers, not civilians.
Are you sympathetic with Hamas's cause?
And do you think that's in part why you've been able to negotiate the release of Thai citizens?
I sympathize with the Palestinian people.
After more and more wars, the land was taken and eventually Palestinians were refugees and made second-class citizens.
You don't have to be a Muslim to have sympathy for Palestinians.
Do you think that Hamas was justified in taking hostages from Israel?
Yes, because there are more than 6,000 Palestinians captured in the past and their families can't visit them.
No one heard their cries.
The world didn't hear their cries.
That's why Hamas had to do this, to get the world's attention focused on Israel's treatment of the Palestinians.
They want to negotiate more and achieve change to get help for the people of Gaza.